Guide to the Division of Student Affairs Records RG 5
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Division of Student Affairs Records
1926-2006
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Western Connecticut State University. Division of Student Affairs
RG 5
22.75 Linear Feet, 23 boxes
The Division of Student Affairs is responsible for oversight of university functions affecting student life and for setting and enforcing related policies. The division's records consist of administrative information, committee files, annual reports, and budgetary records as well as files pertaining to student organizations. The records of the Division of Student Affairs span the dates 1926'-2006, and are organized into seven series: (1) Athletics/Recreation, (2) Campus Ministries, (3) Career Development Center, (4) The Counseling Center, (5) Health Services, (6) Housing/Residential Life, (7) Student Life, and (8) Student Affairs.
Provenance
Transferred to the Archives in 2004.
Access Restrictions
Some material is restricted.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Division of Student Affairs is responsible for oversight of university functions affecting student life and for setting and enforcing related policies. The division's records consist of administrative information, committee files, annual reports, and budgetary records as well as files pertaining to student organizations.
The Greek Council is the governing body for all Western Connecticut State University social fraternities and sororities.
The Forum Club was founded in 1928 by Dr. K. Augusta Sutton, Professor of History and Government. The club provided an opportunity for those interested in public affairs to study and discuss them more fully than in a class situation. The club was affiliated with the International Relations Clubs program of the Carnegie Endowment Association for International Peace.
The Student Government Association (SGA), formerly known as the Student Cooperative Government Association and Cooperative Government Association (CGA), was established in 1928 by Lothrop Higgins, the second president of DNS. The SGA is the sole governing body of the student organizations at WCSU. Its purpose is to coordinate all campus organizations, and to promote and protect the interests, education and welfare of students. See also Record Group 7, Student Organizations: Student Government Association.
Scope and Content Note
The records of the Division of Student Affairs span the dates 1926-2006, and are organized into seven series: (1) Athletics/Recreation, (2) Campus Ministries, (3) Career Development Center, (4) The Counseling Center, (5) Health Services, (6) Housing/Residential Life, (7) Student Life, and (8) Student Affairs.
The Greek Council materials in Series 7 contain minutes of meetings, treasurer's reports, annual reports, and the original petition for establishing a chapter of Kappa Delta Pi, Epsilon XI Chapter, at Danbury State Teachers College. A scrapbook created by Kappa Delta Pi containing newspaper clippings regarding their campus activities can be found in Box 3.
The Student Press Committee created the majority of the scrapbooks in this series. The scrapbooks contain newspaper clippings from Danbury and regional newspapers, which contain news items related to or involving the school's faculty, staff, students, and alumni. In addition, Lilly George created a scrapbook of memorabilia collected during a student trip to Washington, D. C. in February 1952.
This series also contains information regarding The Forum Club. The Forum Club scrapbook contains a collection of memorabilia such as membership lists, invitations, programs, and newspaper articles concerning the club and its annual dinner and guest speaker.
Series 1 Athletics/Recreation, 1950-1999 (w/gaps); Box 1; Arranged in chronological order.; Booklets, sports schedules, and information pamphlets.
Series 2 Campus Ministries, 1954-2001 (w/gaps); Box 1; Arranged in chronological order.; Pamphlets and flyers.
Series 3 Career Development Center, 1972-2000; Boxes 1, 6, and Oversized 2; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.; Annual Reports, newsletters, and poster.
Series 4 The Counseling Center, 1988-1999 (w/gaps); Box 1; Arranged in alphabetical order.; Correspondence, newsletters, and reports.
Series 5 Health Services, 1978-2001 (w/gaps); Box 1; Arranged in chronological order.; Correspondence and pamphlets.
Series 6 Housing/Residential Life, 1941-1962 (w/gaps); Box 1 and Oversized 2; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.; Duty books, housekeeping inventories, minutes, receipts and disbursements, dorm songs, and housing regulations.
Series 7 Student Life, 1926-2006 (w/gaps); Boxes 2-6, 18, and Oversized 1-2; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.Bulletins, handbooks, flyers, manuals, minutes, programs, publications, and scrapbooks.
Series 8 Student Affairs, 1926-2003 (w/gaps); Boxes 7-18, and Oversized 2; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.Annual reports, audits, bulletins, journals, handbooks, manuals, policies and procedures, programs and services, publications, and videotapes.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically in each series.
The files are grouped into 8 series:
Missing Title
Athletics/Recreation, 1950-1999
Campus Ministries, 1954-2001
Career Development Center, 1972-2000
The Counseling Center, 1988-1999
Health Services, 1978-2001
Housing/Residential Life, 1941-1962
Student Life, 1926-2006
Student Affairs, 1926-2003
Related Material
Student Government Association Records
Student Publications Records
Separated Material
Some photographs and publications have been removed and placed in the WCSU Miscellanea Collection and Student Publications Collection. Issues of the student newspaper, The Echo, have been removed and are filed separately under Student Publications.
Fliers (printed matter); Greek Letter Societies -- Connecticut -- Danbury.; Drug abuse -- Prevention -- Directories .; Clippings.; Reports.; Publications.; Substance abuse -- Prevention.; Danbury (Conn.); Correspondence.; Scrapbooks.; College student orientation -- United States; College students -- United States -- Alcohol use -- Directories.; College student government -- Connecticut -- Danbury (Conn); College students -- United States -- Alcohol use -- Prevention -- Directories.; College students -- United States.; College students -- Drug use -- United States -- Directories.; Student Service.; People with disabilities -- Education -- United States; Universities and colleges.; Students -- Recreation.; Students, Foreign -- Connecticut -- Danbury; Child care services -- Connecticut .; College freshmen -- United States.; Minority college students -- United State .; Alcoholism -- Prevention -- Directories; NHA.; The Forum Club.; University of California, Los Angeles. Laboratory for Research in Higher Education.; University of South Carolina. Center for the Study of the Freshmen Year Experience.; FIPSE.; Marley, Lord; Western Connecticut State University; NAFSA.; Americans With Disabilities Act.; Amey, Marilyn J.; Cooperative Institutional Research Program.; Dey, Eric L.; American Council on Education.; Western Connecticut State University. Student Government Association.; Upcraft, M. Lee
- 1. Athletics/Recreation
  - Intercollegiate Sports, 1969-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Intercollegiate Sports, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Men's Athletic Association News, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Recreation Program, 1950-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Women's Athletic Association, 1952-2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    General note
    w/ gaps
- 2. Campus Ministries
  - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
  - Pamphlets and flyers, 1954-2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 3. Career Development Center
  - Annual Reports, 1987-2000 (Box 1, Folder 11-28)
  - Career Connection, 1988-1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Career Connection, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Career and Vocational Planning, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - CDC Search, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 33-35)
  - Pamphlets, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Placement Report, Class of 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Poster, undated (Box OS 2, Folder *)
- 4. Counseling Center, The
  - Counseling Center, 1988-2011 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Counselor Search, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - The Counselor, Vol. 1, Issue 2, August 1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- 5. Health Services
  - Correspondence, 12/78, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Pamphlets, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- 6. Housing/Residential Life
  - Dorm Records: Duty Books, 1953-1961 (Box 1, Folder 43-50)
  - Dorm Records: Equipment Inventory, 1941 (Box OS 2)
  - Dorm Records: Housekeeping Inventories, 1941-1954 (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
  - Dorm Records: Housekeeping Misc., 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 53-54)
  - Dorm Records: Minutes, 1948-1960 (Box 1, Folder 55-62)
  - Dorm Records: Receipts and Disbursements, 1930-1962 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Dorm Records: Songs, undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Dorm Records: Student Housing Regulations, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Guide to Housing & Residence Life, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Pamphlets, undated (Box 1, Folder 67-69)
- 7. Student Life
  - Clubs and Organizations
    - Arts Festival Club, 1978-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Bowling, 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ECHO/FOI, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ECHO-Correspondence, 1975-1989 (Box 2, Folder 4-9)
    - ECHO-Memos, Etc., 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Economics Club, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Greek Council of WCSU, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Chi Alpha, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Delta Kappa Gamma, Iota Chapter, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Delta Phi Omega, 1978-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Delta Sigma Phi, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Kappa Delta Pi, Epsilon XI Chapter, 1943-1961 (Box 2, Folder 17-21)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Phi Alpha Theta, 1973-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Phi Beta Kappa Concert Programs, 1929-1935 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Psi-Chi, 1971-1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Sigma Alpha Iota (Zeta Mu Chapter), 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Sigma Chi Colony, The Wild Colonial Calendar, 1987 (Box OS 2)
    - Greek Council of WCSU: Tau Gamma Alpha, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Guide to Campus Organizations, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 27-29)
    - History Society, 1988-2004 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - History Society: WCSU Outstanding Student Organization, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - PAC (Program Activities Council), 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 31-34)
    - PAC (Program Activities Council), Slides, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
    - PAC (Program Activities Council) Minutes/Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
    - Psychology Club, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Record Book of the Class of 1943, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Rotaract Club of WCSC, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Scrapbook: Forum Club, 1928-1945 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook: Kappa Delta Pi, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook: DNS/DSTC, 1934-1938 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook: DSTC, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1940-1941 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1941 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1941-1944 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook (copies), 1947-1954 (Box 4, Folder 1-8)
    - Scrapbook, 1948-1970 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1952 (Box 3, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1954-1957 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1957-1959 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook: WCSC, 1971-1972 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook: WCSU, 1980-1989 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook: WCSU, 1981-1982 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
    - Scrapbook: Western Rebel Rugby Club, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Scrapbook: WXCI, 1976-1990 (Box 2, Folder 41-46)
  - General
    - Commuter Connections, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 47-49)
    - Historians Craft (HIS 490), 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 50-51)
    - Programs, 1922-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1-26)
    - Student Activities Fund, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 52-53)
    - Student Center, 1979-2006 (Box 2, Folder 54-62)
    - Student Center, Annual Report, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Student Center Board Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 64-65)
    - Student Center Board-Minutes, 1981-1990 (Box 6, Folder 1-6)
    - Student Center Board-Minutes/Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7-10)
  - Student Government Association (SGA)
    - C.G.A. Bulletins, 1948-1954 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
    - Bylaws, Constitution, and Philosophy, 1948-1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1926-1966 (Box 6, Folder 14-24)
    - Senate Legislation, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 25-27)
    - SGA, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 28-32)
    - Student Life Committee, 1966-1990 (Box 6, Folder 33-39)
    - Student Orientation Packet, 2003-2004 (Box OS 2)
- 8. Student Affairs
  - General A - P
    - AAUW Scholarship, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ADA, Audit, Transition Plan, and Policy Statement For Higher Education; Manual and Workbook, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2-6)
    - ADA, Self-Evaluation Programs Worksheets, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7-14)
    - ADA, Self-Evaluation Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 15-24)
    - Advisor's Manual for Student Organizations, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Advisor's Manual for Student Organizations (c.2), 1992 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 27-39)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 40-43)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: The ACA Journal (Winter 1988, December 1988) (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Alcohol and Other Use Survey, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Biennial Review, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 46-49)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Clippings and Photographs, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 50-51)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Core Drug and Alcohol Survey, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 52-57)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Drugs and Alcohol: A Comparative Study of Use & Attitudes, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Substance Abuse Coordinator, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 59-61)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Substance Abuse Coordinator Search, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 62-65)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Substance Abuse & Prevention Program, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 66-67)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: NIDA NOTES, 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 68-69)
    - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Task Force: Year End Report, May 1995 (Box 7, Folder 70-72)
    - Alcoholic Beverages, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Alexander Retirement Party, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports (Restrictions apply), 1987-1996 (Box 8, Folder 2-38)
    - Basic Studies, 1973-1991 (Box 8, Folder 39-49)
    - Budget, 1986-1993 (Box 8, Folder 50-60)
    - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 1-15)
    - Budget, Non-General Fund Acts, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 16-18)
    - Budget, General Fund Accounts, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 19-26)
    - Budget, Statements/Non-General Fund Items, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 27-29)
    - Budget, Statements of Account, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 30-37)
    - Child Care, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 38-42)
    - Child Care - Beal Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 43-45)
    - Child Care, Board of Governors Report, September 1987 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Child Care Commission, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 47-49)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Annual Report, October 18, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: DHE Survey, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Day Care Senate ad Hoc Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Day Care Misc., 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Kershnar Presentation, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: National Coalition for Campus Child Care, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Philip Morris Study, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Proposal, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Proposed Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Child Care Connections of Western Connecticut: Child Care, RA/Y/WCSU Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Child Care, RA/Y/WCSU: Scholarship, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Child Care, RA/Y/WCSU: Statement of Agreement, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Child Care, RA/Y/WCSU: Steering Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 4-7)
    - Child Care, RA/Y/WCSU: Child Care, Resources & References, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Child Care: Survey, May 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Child Care: WCSU Activity, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10-11)
    - Child Care: WCSU Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 12-17)
    - WCSU Child Care Center Contract, 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 65-66)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program), 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 18-21)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program): Program, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program): Freshman Surveys (computer printout), 1990 (Box OS 2)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program): Freshman Survey, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program): Freshman Surveys, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24-32)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program): The American Freshman: National Norms for Fall 1990 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program): The American Freshman: National Norms for Fall 1993 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - CIRP (Cooperative Institutional Research Program): Supplemental Data Reports, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 35-44)
    - CIRP 3-Year Comparisons, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 45-46)
    - Clambake, 1986-1999 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Class of 1989, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Class of 1990, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - College Union Board, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 50-52)
    - Commencement Activities Committee, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Folder 53-58)
    - Conn CAP/Excel Expenses, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 59-60)
    - Contract Log, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Dean of Students, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 62-64)
    - Family Weekend, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
    - Feldman Memos, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Financial Aid (Restrictions apply), 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Financial Aid, Asst. to Dir. Search, January 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Accounts, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Budget (bulk 1990-1993), 1984-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9-16)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Consortium Grant, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 17-20)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Consortium Grant, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 21-23)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Consortium Minutes, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Core Committee, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Drug Prevention Program, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): FIPSE Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 27-31)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Grant, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 32-36)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Grant Proposal, 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Grantee Meeting, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 38-54)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Project Abstracts, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - FIPSE (Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education): Training Workshop, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 56-64)
    - Flyers and Pamphlets, 1967-2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Interns, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Graduating Class Survey (Deegan Study), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Graduating Class Survey (Gernert), 1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Graduating Class Survey, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Graduating Class Survey (Deegan Study), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 6-8)
    - Graduating Class Survey, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Graduation, December 1989 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Guiding Documents, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 11-19)
    - Handbook, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 20-25)
    - Homecoming, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 26-36)
    - Homecoming-Echo, 1987-1992 (Box Filed Separately)
    - I.B.M. Faculty Fellow, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - I.B.M. Faculty Loan Program, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - ISEP (International Student Exchange Program): Enrollments, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - ISEP (International Student Exchange Program): Pre-1989, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 40-45)
    - ISEP (International Student Exchange Program): Report, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - ISEP (International Student Exchange Program): Study Abroad, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Judicial Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 48-50)
    - Judicial Advisory Council, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 51-61)
    - Judicial Affairs, 1984-1993 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Judicial System, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Memorabilia, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Mentor News, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Mentor Project, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 2-7)
    - Mentor Workshop, 1987 (Box 13, Folder *)
    - Mentoring Project, WCSU/AAUW, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 9-12)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Materials, 1992-1998 (Box 18, Folder *)
      The American Freshman: National Norms For Fall 1992
      The BACCHUS Beat, 1997 (w/gaps)
      Beginning Your Journey; A Guide for New Professionals In Student Affairs, 1998 (2c)
      Designing Successful Transitions: A Guide for Orienting Students to College, 1993
      Issues in Advising the Undecided College Student, 1995
      A Handbook for Complying with the Program & Review Requirements of the 1989 Amendments to the Drug-Free Schools and Communities Act, 1992
      In Our Own Backyard; Sexual Harassment in Connecticut's Public High Schools, Executive Summary, 1995
      Network Directory; The Network of Colleges and Universities Committed to the Elimination of Drug and Alcohol
      Abuse, July 1993 and September 1995
      Principles of Good Practice for Student Affairs, Statement And Inventories, 1998
      Sexual Harassment Prevention: Training Consultants, 1994
    - NAMES Project, AIDS Memorial Quilt, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 14-25)
    - NAMES Project, Common Threads, Stories from the Quilt (VHS), 1989 (Box 18, Folder *)
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (NAFSA): Adviser's Manual of Federal Regulations Affecting Foreign Students and Scholars, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 26-30)
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (NAFSA): Adviser's Manual of Federal Regulations Affecting Foreign Students and Scholars 2000 Edition with updates through May 2001 (Includes Addendum to 2001 Updates), 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 31-36)
    - National Association of Foreign Student Advisors (NAFSA): Annual Conference, 52nd: 2000 Immigration Update, Document Collection (Box 13, Folder 37-40)